[energetic music]
[充满活力的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
Oh... hey!
哦……嘿！
- See them flip...
- Aah!
- 看到它们翻转...
- 啊啊！
Ha ha ha ha ha!
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈！
See them soar...
看着他们翱翔......
see them juggle
and so much more.
看他们杂耍
还有更多。
It's Circus Sea Fleas!
这是马戏团海跳蚤！
[honk honk honk]
[喇叭喇叭喇叭]
And they were born
to please you.
他们出生了
来取悦你。
- Ha ha ha ha ha!
- 哈哈哈哈哈哈！
Yay! We love you,
Circus Sea Fleas.
耶！我们爱你，
马戏团海跳蚤。
And the fleas love you.
跳蚤爱你。
Remember, Circus Sea Fleas
live to perform just for you!
记住，马戏团海跳蚤
只为你而活！
We've been
emotionally validated.
我们曾经
情感上得到验证。
Send for your very own
Circus Sea Fleas today!
发送给您自己的
今天马戏团海跳蚤！
Oh...
哦...
I sent for mine yesterday,
and I'm still waiting.
我昨天寄了我的，
我还在等待。
- Bummer, dude!
- What?
- 真糟糕，伙计！
- 什么？
Bummer Dude action figures.
Bummer Dude 可动玩偶。
They're miserable.
[all moaning]
他们很痛苦。
[全都呻吟]
Oh...
哦...
Hey, hey, hey SpongeBob.
嘿嘿嘿海绵宝宝
Got a buncha great stuff
for you today.
得到了一些很棒的东西
今天给你。
The new "Spatula Emporium"
catalog.
新的“抹刀商场”
目录。
No.
不。
Free money from
the sweepstakes you won.
免费资金来自
您赢得的抽奖。
No.
不。
A letter from your family.
一封来自你家人的信。
No.
Packages, how about packages?
不。
套餐，套餐怎么样？
You have any packages for me?
你有什么包裹要给我吗？
No packages.
没有包裹。
Sorry to disappoint you, SpongeBob.
抱歉让你失望了，海绵宝宝。
What makes you think
I'm disappointed?
是什么让你觉得
我很失望？
Everything's just fine.
一切都很好。
Man, what a sad sponge.
伙计，真是一块悲伤的海绵。
That's right,
introducing Sad Sponge,
没错，
介绍悲伤海绵，
The newest Bummer Dude
action figure.
最新的无赖家伙
可动人偶。
Oh...
哦...
And kick, and twist, and kick.
然后踢，扭，踢。
Higher ladies.
I said higher.
高等女士。
我说更高。
I'll show you high.
我会向你展示高。
[groaning]
[呻吟]
Huh?
啊？
[sizzling]
Aah!
[嘶嘶声]
啊啊！
Feel the burn.
感受燃烧的感觉。
I feel it!
我感觉到了！
Ahh...
啊...
[doorbell rings]
Huh?
[门铃响]
啊？
Oh. Pink leg warmers?
哦。粉色暖腿套？
- Yeah, so?
- So...
- 是啊，所以？
- 所以...
I love 'em!
我爱他们！
We're leg warmer buddies.
- Oh, please.
我们是暖腿伙伴。
- 哦，拜托。
I wouldn't be caught dead
in leg warmers with that hat.
我不会被抓死
戴着那顶帽子的暖腿套。
Go back to fashion school.
回到时装学校。
[sighs]
He's right.
[叹气]
他是对的。
Hello, fashion school?
I'm coming back!
你好，时装学校吗？
我回来了！
I'm reborn!
我重生了！
What?
This package isn't even for me.
什么？
这个包裹甚至不适合我。
It's for SpongeBob.
这是给海绵宝宝的。
Hmph.
哼。
That mailman is a moron.
那个邮递员是个白痴。
[overlapping yelling, whooping]
[重叠的喊叫、呼喊]
[fleas muttering, whooping]
[跳蚤低语，呼喊]
And time for me to eat.
还有我吃饭的时间。
[fleas yelling, chattering]
[跳蚤大喊大叫，叽叽喳喳]
And...
和...
Bowl is nice and clean.
[humming]
碗又漂亮又干净。
[嗡嗡声]
Grab my favorite spoon.
[humming]
拿起我最喜欢的勺子。
[嗡嗡声]
Brush on my shirt.
[humming]
刷在我的衬衫上。
[嗡嗡声]
Milk is smelling fresh.
[humming]
牛奶闻起来很新鲜。
[嗡嗡声]
[fleas clamoring, chattering]
[跳蚤吵闹，喋喋不休]
Cereal gives me pep.
[humming]
麦片让我充满活力。
[嗡嗡声]
[fleas yelling, whooping]
[跳蚤大喊大叫]
It's moving by itself.
[humming]
它自己在移动。
[嗡嗡声]
Ghosts are in my bowl.
[humming]
鬼魂在我的碗里。
[嗡嗡声]
Ghosts are in my bowl?
我碗里有鬼？
Ghosts are in my bowl!
我碗里有鬼！
[eerie music]
[怪异音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Huh?
啊？
[gasps]
[喘气]
Aah!
啊啊！
My kitchen's haunted!
我的厨房闹鬼了！
Calm down, Squidward.
冷静点，章鱼哥。
You're just seeing things
because you're so tired.
你只是看到了一些东西
因为你太累了。
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
You just need some more sleep.
是啊是啊，就是这样。
你只是需要多睡一会儿。
♪ ♪
♪♪
[snoring softly]
[轻柔的鼾声]
[fleas clamoring, whooping]
[跳蚤的叫喊声、呼喊声]
[fanfare, crowd cheering]
[大张旗鼓，人群欢呼]
Huh?
啊？
What? Oh...
什么？哦...
I must still be dreaming.
我一定还在做梦。
[lively circus music]
[热闹的马戏音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Blblblblb.
Huh?
blblbllb。
啊？
Hup... hup...
呼……呼……
hup... huh!
呼……呼！
Huh-huh-huh-huh...
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈...
♪ ♪
Welcome to your Sea Flea Circus.
欢迎来到您的海跳蚤马戏团。
It's our duty to entertain you.
招待您是我们的责任。
How delightful.
多么令人愉快啊。
Huh?
啊？
Amazing.
惊人的。
♪ ♪
Huh? What's next?
啊？接下来怎么办？
[twirr]
[旋转]
Lunchtime.
午餐时间。
Lunchtime?
午餐时间？
Why would a dream need a...
为什么梦想需要...
Aah!
啊啊！
This isn't a dream!
这不是梦！
It's an infestation!
这是一种感染！
Huh?
Where'd they go?
啊？
他们去哪儿了？
Oh! Hmm...
Not bad.
哦！嗯...
不错。
Aah! Aah!
啊啊！啊啊！
I look amazing. Please don't
ruin this by biting my face.
我看起来棒极了。请不要
咬我的脸毁了这一切。
Aah! You ruined it.
啊啊！你毁了它。
Ah...
啊...
Why is this happening to me?
为什么这种事会发生在我身上？
Oh, yeah. Karma.
哦，是的。业力。
[gong echoes]
[锣声回响]
Help!
Ooh...
帮助！
哦...
Hey? What are you...
嘿？你是做什么的...
Oh! That feels nice and warm.
哦！那种感觉又美好又温暖。
It's actually getting
kind of hot now.
实际上正在得到
现在有点热。
Hey. You're trying to cook me.
Let me out of here.
嘿。你想把我煮熟了
让我离开这里。
Parsnip?
Puh!
防风草？
噗！
Are you crazy?
你疯了？
You don't serve a prime piece
of meat like me with parsnip.
你没有提供优质作品
像我这样的肉加防风草。
You need lemons
to brighten my flavors
你需要柠檬
来提亮我的口味
and some pepper or spice.
和一些胡椒或香料。
Ah! Much better.
啊!好多了。
Now let me out of here!
现在让我离开这里！
Aah!
啊啊！
[Squidward screaming, yelling]
[章鱼哥尖叫，大喊]
Now you're cookin'.
现在你开始做饭了。
Huh? Oh, no,
my buttons are tarnished.
啊？哦，不，
我的纽扣失去光泽了。
No circus flea is going to want
马戏团的跳蚤不会想要
to perform for a guy
with tarnished buttons.
为一个男人表演
带有失去光泽的按钮。
Fa la la la la la!
啦啦啦啦啦！
[horn toots distantly]
[gasps] Circus music?
[远处传来喇叭声]
[喘气]马戏音乐？
Hmm.
[horns tooting]
唔。
[喇叭声]
Oh, hey, Squidward.
Just checking.
哦，嘿，章鱼哥。
只是检查。
You've haven't seen a package
addressed to me, have you?
你还没见过包裹
是写给我的吗？
My circus fleas!
Yes!
我的马戏团跳蚤！
是的！
They came! They came!
他们来了！他们来了！
Hey, this box is empty.
Where did the fleas go?
嘿，这个盒子是空的。
跳蚤去哪儿了？
Hello, fleas.
你好，跳蚤。
I hope you fed them, Squidward.
They can get pretty hungry.
我希望你喂饱它们，章鱼哥。
他们可能会很饿。
Oh, I fed them all right.
Please take them away now.
哦，我喂他们没问题。
请现在就把它们带走。
You got it.
你明白了。
Ho! Alley-oop, waah!
嗬！空中接力，哇！
[fleas chattering]
[跳蚤喋喋不休]
Ta-da!
哒哒！
Ha ha ha ha ha!
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈！
Now let's take this circus
to my place.
现在让我们看看这个马戏团
到我的地方。
All aboard!
全部上车！
♪ ♪
[toot toot]
[嘟嘟]
May all your days
be Sea Flea Circus days.
愿你所有的日子
是海跳蚤马戏团的日子。
Best day ever!
有史以来最好的一天！
Stupid circus fleas.
愚蠢的马戏团跳蚤。
Just look at the mess they left.
只要看看他们留下的烂摊子就知道了。
Hmm?
唔？
What's this?
这是什么？
Oh.
[twirr]
哦。
[旋转]
[commotion, yelling]
[骚乱、叫喊]
Aah!
啊！